(gentle guitar music)
♪ I was a little too tall ♪
♪ Could've used a few pounds ♪
♪ Tight pants points
hardly renown ♪
♪ She was a black haired
beauty with big dark eyes ♪
♪ And points all her own
sittin' way up high ♪
♪ Way up firm and high ♪
♪ Out past the cornfields
where the woods got heavy ♪
♪ Out in the back
seat of my '60 Chevy ♪
♪ Workin' on mysteries
without any clues ♪
♪ Workin' on our night moves ♪
♪ Tryin' to make some
front page drive-in news ♪
♪ Workin' on our night moves ♪
♪ In the summertime ♪
♪ In the sweet summertime ♪
♪ We weren't in love
oh no far from it ♪
♪ We weren't searchin' for
some pie in the sky summit ♪
♪ We were just young
and restless and bored ♪
♪ Livin' by the sword ♪
♪ And we'd steal away
every chance we could ♪
♪ To the backroom, the
alley, the trusty woods ♪
♪ I used her she used me ♪
♪ But neither one cared ♪
♪ We were gettin' our share ♪
♪ Workin' on our night moves ♪
♪ Tryin' to lose the
awkward teenage blues ♪
♪ Workin' on our night moves ♪
♪ And it was summertime ♪
♪ Sweet summertime, summertime ♪
♪ And oh the wonder ♪
♪ Felt the lightning ♪
♪ And we waited on the thunder ♪
♪ Waited on the thunder ♪
♪ I awoke last night to
the sound of thunder ♪
♪ How far off I
sat and wondered ♪
♪ Started hummin'
a song from 1962 ♪
♪ Ain't it funny how
the night moves ♪
♪ When you just don't seem
to have as much to lose ♪
♪ Strange how the night moves ♪
♪ With autumn closing in ♪
♪ (gentle guitar strumming) ♪
♪ Night moves, night moves ♪
♪ Night moves, yeah ♪
♪ Night moves ♪
♪ I sure remember
the night moves ♪
♪ Night moves ♪
♪ Workin' and practicin' ♪
♪ Oh the night moves ♪
♪ Night moves, night moves ♪
♪ Oh, night moves ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, I remember ♪